And the artists began to mingle and
work with us.
The artists almost came to disturb us
with their pizzeria.  To date, there have been
331 visits [music] by artists who have
worked inside the factory and have
produced an incredible body of work.  The first
memory that comes to mind is
that of Yoko Ono who came here.  I
was 5 or 6 years old, in short, and for me
interacting with girls with
almond-shaped eyes was truly an
incredible thing, especially because for lunch we
might eat tofu, soy and seitan.
All the foods that for a 6-
year-old were taste surprises, but
not pleasant surprises.  I remember
the disgusted faces I made when
I ate certain oriental flavors.